Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Fair Trade, 1988-2012; Series 2
  - Fresh Cut Flowers, 1998-2012; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Sintrasplendor/Dole meeting, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Sintrasplendor Speaking Tour, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Sintrasplendor Tour, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Sintrapacna-Colombia flowers, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Social Accountability International (SAI) conference, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Social Accountability Conference, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Unuidad Agraria, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Untraflores, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Untraflores-Louise Mellon, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Valentine's Day Tour-notes, 2005-2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Alejandro Torres communications [1], 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Alejandro Torres communications [2], 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-flowers, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Oversize 81, Folder 1)
    - Colombia flowers-USLEAP correspondence, 2006-2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Dole, Splendor, and Ministry of Social Protection, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Dole-Jan Schakowsky, 2006-2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Dole proposed agreement, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Dole-Central Unitarie de Trabajadores, 2006-2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Dole flower press, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Dole, Ministry of Social Protection, 2006-2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Dole "restructuring", 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Dole updates, Colombia, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Flower Certification Standards, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Flower Certification, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Flower Industry-assorted, 2006-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Flowers, Italy, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Flower videos, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Flower Worker Tour, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Flower Workers Committee, Miami, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Flower Industry Workshop Materials [1], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Flower workshop communications [2], 2006-2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Flores la Fragrancia, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Miami-flower events, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Miami-Mothers Day Action, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Miami-Valentine's Day Tour, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Mother's Day event-notes, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Signed Letters to Dole Fresh Flowers (Valentine's Day Tour), 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Sintraflor meeting-April 2006, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Sinaltraflor/Utracun, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Planning Session-USLEAP/Sintrasplendor, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Untrafragancia [1], 2006-2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Untrafragancia [2], 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Untraflores workshops, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles-Valentine's Day Tour, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Valentine's Day Tour-Visa Process, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Valentine's Day Tour, logistics, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Bochica flower workers, La Ceja, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Colombia Flower Industry research, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Dole Fresh Flowers communications, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Flower Industry research, 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Flower plantation, La Ceja, Antioquia, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Flower Meeting-April 2007, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Florverde, 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - "Rose & Lavaro: Dal Kenya all'Italia l'incredible viaggiodei friori" by Raitano and Calvi, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Valentine's Day Report: Flower Plantations in Colombia and Ecuador, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Colombia flowers, 2008-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Dole/Intenational Brotherhood of the Teamsters, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Dora Acero Tour, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Ethical Training Initiative-Colombia, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Fair Trade flowers, Colombia, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Fair Trade flowers, Colombia, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Flower Certification, 2008-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Flowers, Colombia, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Flower Worker Tour, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Global Underwriters-Insurance for Colombia, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Interfaith sign-on, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Papagayo-Alejandro Torres, 2008-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Sinaltraflor, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Untraflores/Sinaltraflor, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Colombia flowers/Untraflores, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Colombia trip/flowers, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Colombia University-Fairness in Flowers project, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-Untraflores, 2009-2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Flower booklet drafts, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Gendered Injustice: The Struggle of Women Flower Workers in Colombia, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Papagayo Flowers, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Colombia flower industry, 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - National Commission of Human Rights, 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Sunburst Farms, 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Colombian/Belgian flower projects, 2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Flower correspondence regarding Mario Nannetti, 2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Untraflores, Colombia flowers, 2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - World Day for Working Rights in Mexico, 2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Falcon Farms, Colombia, 2012; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Message from KMBT_363, 2012; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Starbucks Coffee, 1989-2009; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Cafe Mam brochure, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Chentex Evaluation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Providence, Rhode Island, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Specialty Coffees-Business Listing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Starbucks Coffee-Guatemalan Workers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Starbucks flyer drafts [1], undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Starbucks brochure drafts [2], 1989-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Starbucks catalogs [4], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Starbucks flyer and brochure drafts [5], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks brochure draft [6], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks brochures [7], 1999-2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks brochures, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala Coffee Research [1], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala Coffee Research [2], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Research-Guatemala Coffee [3], 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Coffee and Pesticides, 1992-1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Houston, Texas, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Starbucks [1], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Starbucks [2], 1995-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Starbucks [3], 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Starbucks [4], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Starbucks [5], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks [6], 1997-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks article drafts, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks-US/GLEP correspondence [1], 1994-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Starbucks correspondence-US/GLEP [2], 1994-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Starbucks/ USGLEP correspondence [3], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Starbucks correspondence [4], 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Starbucks correspondence [5], 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Starbucks correspondence and press, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Starbucks draft letters, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Starbucks campaign-grassroots [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Starbucks campaign-grassroots [2], 1994-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Starbucks campaign-grassroots [3], undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Starbucks campaign kit materials [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Starbucks campaign kit materials [2], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Starbucks campaign kit materials [3], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Kit-Starbucks [4], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Starbucks Mailings-Campaign, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Starbucks Corporate Information [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Starbucks Corporation annual and quarterly reports [2], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks Corporation Reports [3], 1995-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks Annual report [4], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks Annual Reports [5], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Starbucks press [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Starbucks press [2], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Starbucks press [3], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Starbucks stock, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Starbucks strategy [1], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Starbucks strategy [2], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Strategy/consultation [3], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Starbucks Shareholder action [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Starbucks Annual Shareholders meeting [2], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Starbucks shareholder information [3], 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Code of Conduct, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Coffee Notes [1], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Coffee Notes [2], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - A Campaign for Justice for Coffee Workers [1], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Justice for Coffee Workers Campaign [2], 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta, Georgia [1], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Chicago [2], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Dallas, Texas [3], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Minneapolis, Minnesota [4], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - New York [5], 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Seattle, Washington [6], 1994-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Vancouver/Portland [7], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Report on Guatemala Vol.15 No.4-coffee, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - UFCW, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - ANACAFE [1], 1995-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - ANACAFE [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - ANACAFE and Starbucks [3], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Chicago Tribune-Stephen Coats Article, March 13, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Code of Conduct [1], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Code of Conduct/CARE [2], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Starbucks Commitment newsletter-Code of Conduct [3], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Analysis of Stabucks Framework for Code of Conduct [4], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - 1996 Status Report and 1997 Action Plan [5], 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - December 1996 Analysis of Progress in Implementing Code of Conduct [6], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Analysis of Starbucks 1996 Progress and1997 Action Plan on Implementin the Starbucks Code of Conduct [7], Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Code of Conduct/CRLN [8], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Stabucks Code of Conduct progress analysis [9], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Boston, Massachusetts, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Denver/Boulder, Colorado, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - International Labour Conference Convention, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - International Union of Food, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - "Gang of Four"-John Boonstra, Dan Cantrell, Robby stern, Ron Judd, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Labor Link-Starbucks, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Patricia Close and David Foecke (donors) correspondence, 1995-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - The Progressive-Vol. 59, No.3, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Seattle meetings, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Starbucks campaign, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Starbucks Press contacts, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Meeting Notes [1]-Starbucks, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Meeting Notes [2]-Starbucks, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Starbucks Meetings [3], 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks notes [1], 1995-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks notes [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Statement of Beliefs/Code of Conduct, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Stock Certificate-Starbucks, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Student Correspondence-Starbucks, 1995-1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Dying for a Cup of Coffee by Kristin M Anderson, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles, California, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Miscellanous Cities, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - San Diego, California, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - San Franciso, California, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Starbucks [1], 1995-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Starbucks [2], 1997-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Washington, D.C., 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Coffee Research, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Conference Proceedings-1st Sustainable Coffee Congress, 1996; Serues 2 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Campaign history notes-Starbucks, 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Eastside Week, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Franklin Research and Development Corporation, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Implementation of Code of Conduct, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - KLD & Company, Incorporated and Working Assets, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Miscellanous Correspondence, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Smithsonian Migratory Bird Center & Sustaniable Coffee Congress, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Sustainable Coffe Conference, 1996-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Starbucks Press Kit [1], 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Starbucks Press Kit [2], 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Presskit-Starbucks [3], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Starbucks Campaign Press Kit/Misc. Materials [4], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Assorted Starbucks, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ATI/Meso-America, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Canadian Auto-Workers, Starbucks, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Coffee-Germany Correspondence [1], 1997-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Coffee-Netherlands, correspondence [2], 1998-2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - First Sustainable Coffee Congress, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Form Letters-Starbucks, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Grassroots Communications, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Headwaters International, Incorporated, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Media-Scott Pearson material [1], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Media-King TV [2], 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Media-NBC Dateline [3], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Media-ABC News [4], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Media-CBC Television [5], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Oxfam Canada, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Starbucks-Laird Harris Public Affairs, 1997-1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Starbucks Press Conference, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Starbucks Analysis, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Starbucks Framework for Action, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Starbucks Progress Report drafts [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Starbucks Progress Updates [2], 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Fair Trade Labeling Organization (FLO) study [1], 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Fair Trade Labeling Organization (FLO) study [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Fair Trade Coffee Correspondence [3], 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Fair Trade Coffee/Proctor and Gamble [4], 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - The Fresh Cup [1], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fresh Cup Magazine-June 2001-"Coffee Almanac", 1998-2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Coffee Correspondence [1], 1998-2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Coffee Correspondence [2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Consumer's Choice Council report, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Starbucks/U.S. Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC), 1999-2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Starbucks Update, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - "Warbucks Coffee" brochure, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Coffee Workers in Guatemala-COVERCO Report, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Starbucks Sourcing Guidelines, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks Global Week of Action, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Starbucks Fiscal Annual Report, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Rainforest Alliance-Starbucks [1], 2001; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Rainforest Alliance-Starbucks [2], 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - International Coffee Organization, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Mugged Poverty in your Coffee Cup-Oxfam, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Starbucks Corporate Social Reponsibility reports [1], 2002-2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Starbucks Corporate Social Reponsibility report [2], 2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Starbucks Corporate Responsibility Report [3], 2005-2006; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Starbucks Corporate Social Responsibility Report, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - New York Times-Coffee Articles, September-November 2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Common Code for the Coffee Community, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Starbucks-Seattle Meeting, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks/IWW, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks Preferred Supplier Program, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks reports, Jonathan B. Levine, 2005; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Coffee Industry film, "Black Gold", 2007; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Starbucks C.A.F.E., 2007; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Starbucks-clippings, 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - New York Times-Fair Trade Coffee Article, October 11, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Newsletters, 1992-2012; Series 3
  Materials published by USLEAP are organized chronologically by year. Materials published by different organizations are seperately organized in Subseries 1, Affiliate Newsletters, alphabetically by title. Folders with similiar titles or themes are marked by numbers in brackets to indicate their order.
  - Affiliate Newsletters, 1982-2011; Series 3 Subseries 1
    Materials in this collection are organized chronologically by year. Folder titles within each box are arranged alphabetically. Folders with similiar titles or themes are marked by numbers in brackets to indicate their order.
    - Friedrich Ebert Stiftung, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Green America-Guide to Fair Trade, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Multinational Monitor flyer, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Transnational Information Exchange-Europe [1], 1982-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Transnational Information Exchange-Brazil [2], 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)